Has there been any contact with Count Mazurek?
No. However, we know his landing castle is functional.
If Itzalb Noah is still active, that means Count Mazurek is still among the living.
Perhaps he is lying low and waiting for an opening, and is safe.
Or perhaps he's being held as a prisoner.
Whichever it is, Mazurek's return does not seem likely.
In which case, there is but one course of action.
And what would that be?
I can no longer permit that Earth-born dog to run loose any longer.
Thank you!
Thank you.
Yes, ma'am.
And our Mars night guest?
Not a word. It would seem he's one of the silent type.
Mizusaki, do you know why they're so attractive to us? The silent type?
Uh, because they seem calm and collected?
Because they listen to whatever you have to say.
And our replacement crew?
Oh, yes, ma'am.
All of them are on board.
Station ships are revised to reflect that.
A few of them served with us previously.
Warrant Officer Kaisuka, Lieutenant Marito,
as well as Dr. Yagarai, now an ensign, who is our official medical officer.
Also, Ensign Kaisuka has a request to be able to interrogate the Mars night.
And the reason for that is, he says he wants to try out his analytical engine.
Really? You wrote the code for this yourself, Inaho?
I just made some tweaks to the firmware it was already running.
The connections here are somewhat expanded.
How does it feel?
Not all that different.
You really shouldn't expand it any further than this.
By the time you notice a problem, it'd be too late.
I won't. I'm aware of the risk involved here.
So, this is where you are.
Yuki.
Do you have a minute?
Now, why did you agree to serve on this ship?
What do you mean, why?
There's no reason.
It's not as if they're making you go on fighting.
You should have packed up and gone away as soon as your wounds were all healed.
It's exactly the same thing for you, too.
It's absolutely not.
Because I am a soldier.
There was no valid reason for a young woman like you to be one.
It's the same.
It is not!
I regret it every day.
That I let you become a soldier.
But when I saw you unconscious and covered in blood,
I asked myself,
Why didn't I stop you?
I became one.
To protect you.
I wanted to save you and the world you're such a wonderful part of.
But I failed at it.
I'm sorry.
But you see, I can't just do nothing.
Is it because of the princess?
Because that girl is not the same princess you once knew.
She's now an enemy who's trying to conquer the earth.
That person is a fake.
And the real one is still alive somewhere.
Why would you possibly think that?
Analysis by my left eye.
All the facts add up.
I think that she's being held against her will.
Therefore, I want to rescue the princess.
But that's impossible!
Look, Yuki.
She was in front of me, not more than a foot away.
I was hurt.
She was shot trying to help me.
And that is why I have to save her.
Now!
Long time, Lieutenant.
What condition are they in?
When they completed all the tests,
diagnostics show those gravity waves really did a number on them.
Most of them are going to need an overhaul.
I understand that you're not drinking anymore.
My primary physician is a real nag.
In that case, I guess a toast is out of the question.
Oh, a toast is always in order.
You're just unbelievable.
Hey, that comes straight from my doctor.
Medicinal purposes.
So, how are you feeling?
Well, you don't look very happy.
I heard you were given a full body search.
I never conceived it possible to be subjected to such primitive questioning.
We can't have you using a poison tooth or anything else like that.
What an outdated notion.
Says the knight battling for fame and glory.
From a Terran viewpoint,
I suppose the feudal system of Verse would seem just as anachronistic.
Well, if that is your problem, then why don't you just make a change?
The words of one born into complacency.
You're like pigs freezing to death.
Once you are too cold to move, you've no chance of survival.
You know a great deal.
You admit I'm right?
No, information about pigs.
Princess Asalem had never even seen a bird before.
Princess Asalem? You actually spoke to her?
We were on a ship together.
I see.
So you were one of those who sought to exploit her.
Not exploitation. Cooperation.
Cooperation?
Would you just answer one question?
Do I look like a man who would just blithely sell out his nation?
You don't look like it, or sound like it.
Which makes you the perfect man to ask.
Did you swear an oath of loyalty?
To Her Highness Princess Asalem?
Aren't you going to eat anything, Rye?
If you don't eat something, you won't have any energy if we go into combat.
I'm just not very hungry.
With a fasting diet, the weight comes off your boobs first.
I've never been on a diet, so I wouldn't know about that.
Huh?
What?
You mean you've never ever tried to lose weight?
That's amazing!
How do you keep that trim figure of yours?
Yes, please. I'd like to know that too.
Commander!
Are you having lunch here, ma'am?
Since we're in port, I thought it might be a nice change to eat somewhere other than the ship.
You're right about that. We don't get to eat out much.
Oh yeah, that reminds me.
Has anyone seen Inaho today?
I was going to ask him to join us, but he was already gone.
Ensign Kaiska is busy. He's interrogating the Mars Knight at the moment.
Huh? Inaho is doing that?
I think I'll head back.
Hey! Wait a minute! Hold on a sec!
Hey, Rae!
She never said the secret to her figure.
So what you're telling me is that the Princess Asalem currently at our moon base is not her, but actually an imposter?
Yes.
If true, then where might one find the real Princess Asalem?
Being held as a prisoner somewhere?
Or is there some other reason she cannot show herself?
Possibly both those things.
Your left eye determined that as well?
It's an analytical engine.
Unfortunately, I am not one who is so foolish as to believe such a preposterous tale as that one.
We've retrieved your cataphract and are studying it.
The force of that explosion knocked the old Noah drive offline.
It's a pity it will never be able to function again.
You powered it down yourself, didn't you?
Out of fear that we would steal it.
I told you it stopped working after the explosion.
Did it really?
No.
You intentionally shut it down.
I will say it again.
That is not the real Princess Asalem.
There are many species of birds as well.
There are large birds, and some that are very small.
Others have brilliant colors.
And this is how they fly.
Through the open skies of Earth.
While most birds are fully capable of flying,
there are some that are flightless and remain Earth-bound.
Birds that can't fly?
Princess Asalem might say
that she finds it sad that they cannot fly
even though they are equipped with wings.
She is so kind.
She feels very deeply for others.
Not to worry.
The flightless ones do not miss it.
The ones to pity are those who can fly,
but are kept in cages.
Why would anyone trap them like that?
Because...
They are so very beautiful.
Princess Asalem was shot right in front of me.
And Count Sosbom was the man who did it.
That's preposterous.
At that point, he left with slain Troyard,
taking Princess Asalem along with them.
Count Sosbom is celebrated as the great hero
who rescued Princess Asalem.
He's anything but a hero.
He's the mastermind who planned out her assassination.
No, that cannot be the case.
Those bastards tricked my father,
made him their pawn, and used him.
Then they crushed him like a bug.
So, you were verse-born then.
I see.
In any event,
your father would have certainly died sooner or later.
You should give thanks that he wasn't branded a traitor
and summarily lynched or worse.
What's that supposed to mean?
Are you saying that my father deserved to die?
Let's go.
I'm not done with him.
Come with me.
Let go!
You must think I'm an idiot.
Then I'll always be bound by the past.
Always be its prisoner.
Well, you're right.
I am just like them.
All I do is blame others.
I hate them.
I envy them.
Fight and steal and kill them!
Just a stupid Martian.
No, you are different.
I am not.
You are.
I'm no different than them!
I hate Martians!
And I hate myself more than all of them!
Count Marilsian, you say?
Yes, sir.
He has been calling repeatedly.
He is saying that he wishes to be put through to Princess Asalem.
And what does Sir Slain have to say?
I have been unable to find the Count, sir.
What is this commotion?
Leave us.
Yes, sir.
I see.
Can you not have your discussion with me present?
Sorry, Your Highness.
Unfortunately, even here at the Moonbase, knowledge of your existence is somewhat limited.
Please try to avoid public areas.
Do you think I should speak with him?
It is Count Marilsian, isn't it?
But Your Highness...
Is there a problem?
Patch him through to the throne room.
Her Royal Highness Princess Asalem is most exceedingly gracious.
I beg forgiveness for this disturbance.
Lord Count Marilsian, what a great pleasure.
So now then, what was it that you wished to discuss with me?
To contact me without Count Troyard's leave.
Well, it must be very urgent.
Hm.
It is indeed.
Is his permission required to speak with you, Your Highness?
It seems to be quite overprotective for Count Troyard to keep you essentially under guard like this.
Not the best choice of words, perhaps.
Let us then say instead he is a knight protecting his princess in her ivory tower.
My deepest apologies if I have given offense, comparing Your Highness to a bird in a cage.
A bird in a cage?
As I understand it, an expression used on Earth to describe when deprived of her freedom.
Message from base command.
They say that the prisoner has escaped.
Put the ship on alert.
Notify all duty stations.
Yes, ma'am.
I hate these late-night alarms.
They're just killing me.
Raiyei.
Come on, time to get the lead out.
Raiyei?
So, it's you.
Come on.
Let's get out of here.
Why are you doing this for me?
I want you to go back to your landing castle so you can find out where the real Princess of Salem is being held.
But why would you trust me?
Because I believe you want the same thing Princess of Salem does.
I don't think you ever had any desire to attack the Earth like this.
Your left eye told you that?
I can tell that much without ever using my left eye.
You have made yourself very familiar with the Earth.
Not for invasion purposes.
Your interest lies elsewhere.
Ah, so you do see everything.
There's one other thing I want you to find out for me.
Slain Troyart's objective.
What's his plan?
Keep on a north heading and you'll reach your landing castle.
You'll need to walk from here.
Yes.
Here.
Food and water.
We can't have you dying of thirst before you can make it away.
Though truthfully, that wouldn't bother me one little bit.
If it comes to it, understand that Princess of Salem's well-being may be in your hands.
Before I leave here, might I ask you one thing?
What is your name?
My name is Count Mazurek, a proud member of the 37 clans of the Verse Empire.
Count Mazurek, huh?
There's a type of folk music on Earth with a similar name.
Yes.
As I researched the meaning behind my name, I became more and more fascinated with the Earth.
What is your name?
I'm Inaho.
Inaho Kaizuka.
Count Mazurek, take good care of Princess of Salem.
I shall do so.
Inaho Kaizuka.
Hmm.
Tell me, why'd you ask me to help with this?
What do you mean?
Didn't you stop to think that I might just kill that Martian?
Like I did with the Princess?
I need to point out that you did not in fact kill her.
I failed to kill her.
You're different now.
I am not.
You are.
Give it a rest.
I am not.
You are.
You are no longer the person you were then.
Mustang leader to Mustang 1-1.
What's your status?
Mustang 1-1.
All good.
Stay on alert.
Roger that.
I know.
Why?
What's the meaning of this?
Who authorized those landing castles to dock here?
My lord, it was...
I authorized them to.
Your highness.
Counts Marilsian and Barocruz requested personal audience with Princess of Salem.
So I permitted them to dock.
First as Princess of Salem.
But then...
As the rightful Princess of Verse.
Why would you do such a thing?
Let's be off now.
It would be poor behavior to keep our visitors waiting.
Princess of Salem.
We are both humbled and delighted that your highness would grant us an audience on such extremely short notice.
My lord, Count Marilsian, and my lord, Count Barocruz, I am most grateful to my faithful knights for our orbital defenses.
If times were normal, I expect you would go down to Earth and expand your domains.
We leave the conquest of Earth in the hands of our like-minded brethren.
Your highness needn't worry on that account.
I see. That is good to hear.
If your highness permits, there is a matter of greater importance to address.
With the terrible, tragic death of Count Sosbohm, who will succeed as commander of the Royal Guard charged with protecting the Moonbase and your highness?
You needn't worry about any of that, Count Marilsian.
I shall assume those duties without delay.
Princess of Salem, I have come to beg you to consider if you would do me the honor of allowing me to serve at your side.
I have already told you, Count Marilsian.
I will thank you to keep your lowborn comments to yourself, Terran.
This is a fortress under the flag of the Verse Empire.
If I lost the post to someone like Count Sosbohm, a man of great warrior merit, who rescued her highness, I could approve.
Yet you, who remains a Terran, even if you are his adopted son, actually think that holy post should be yours?
The very thought that one of low blood is setting foot inside the castle where a member of the Verse Imperial family dwells is intolerable.
One without a landing castle is unfit to call himself Count.
You are not qualified to protect this place in any regard.
What then are you suggesting?
That we determine once and for all which should be protecting her highness.
My Herschel and the nobility of my blood, or your hand-me-down Tharsis.
In the presence of all here, Count Troyard, I challenge you to a duel.
Just like that, count on us, let's go!
Let's go!
僕たちは彷徨える未来 彼を探している 僕たちは彷徨える未来 窮屈な空に 光を探している 彼を探している 彼を探している 彼を探している 彼の手は無力で 叫びはまだ遠くて 彼の手は無力で 叫びはまだ遠くて だけど 飛ぶことを恐れてはいない旨ですよね?
I'm looking for a light
The sound of the sound is no power
The sound is still far away
But I'm afraid to fly
I can't be afraid
Even if it's not a long time
Even if it's not a perfect time
And if it's not a world
In coming true
It takes to create a black hole
Even if it's not a perfect time
And if it's not a perfect time
PotGGER
Rây comments
Oh, young doctor!